These little punches are great when you're doing paper cutting designs.
I'm going to use these little symbols to decorate my flags and add a little burst of color; we'll do a little bit of yellow for each one.
And I'll just put a little bit of punched symbol in each of our flags.
You just put the glue, a little more glue and place you're punched out design there.
So all our little symbols also add to the theater feel of our, our place with butterflies and a cupid for love; and flowers for beauty.
We have the moon here, and you need some horses for the knights; and a little teddy bear, a star and a heart.
And to finish off our design I, I've cut out some letters; I've cut out the word puppet's just free hand.
I'm going to start with any lettering you want to start on the middle letter to make sure you have an even placement.
And I've cut the letters free hand, so there just a little fun and jumbled looking.
And instead of cutting out the dots of the letters I used a star in the middle, o.k... And when you're finished laying out all your letters and your little punch shapes, you want to make sure you glaze over the design with decoupage glue.
Nice, and even and smooth; and your design is finished.
And we have a beautiful, colorful traditional style puppet theater.